Guide to the Al Swift Congressional Papers 1885-2003
Western Washington University, Center for Pacific Northwest Studies
Al Swift Congressional Papers
1885-2003
1978-1994
Center for Pacific Northwest Studies Goltz-Murray Building 808 25th St Bellingham, WA 98225-9123 Phone: 360 650 7534 Email: heritage.resources@wwu.edu
XOE_CPNWS0029swift
Swift, Al, 1935-
302 linear ft.
U.S. Congressional Representative Al Swift was active from 1978 to 1994, serving on many committees during his tenure. The records document important issues of the late 1970s through the mid-1990s including campaign finance reform, uniform poll closing, and environmental issues relating to clean air, nuclear waste, the spotted owl, and hydroelectric power. Swift was also considered a legislative expert on telecommunication and broadcasting issues.
Al Swift was born in Tacoma, Washington on September 12, 1935, where he later graduated from Lincoln High School. Swift attended Whitman College in Walla Walla from 1953 to 1955, then graduated in 1957 with a B.A. in Journalism from Central Washington University in Ellensburg. While attending college, Swift began his career in broadcasting by working for local radio stations. After graduation, he joined KVOS Television and Radio in Bellingham, Washington. Swift was promoted to program director of KVOS in 1962.
In 1965, Swift joined Congressman Lloyd Meeds' (D-WA) staff as his first administrative assistant where he remained for the next five years. In 1969, Swift returned to KVOS as news and public affairs director. While at KVOS, he produced many programs on state and local issues and, in the process, won many awards, including the prestigious Emmy award. While in Bellingham, Swift remained active in community affairs. In the early 1970s he played a key roll in rewriting Bellingham's 1906 city charter. By 1975 he had became chairman of a citizen's advisory committee on Bellingham schools and was appointed by Mayor Ken Hertz to the Bellingham Housing Authority.
In 1977 Swift returned to Representative Meeds' staff as his top aide. When Meeds decided to retire, Swift resigned from his position to begin his own campaign for Washington's 2nd Congressional District. Throughout the 1978 campaign Swift was considered the underdog and his first hurdle was to gain the State Democratic Party nomination. Senator Henry Jackson's longtime press secretary, Brian Corcoran, was considered a "shoe-in" for the nomination yet Swift came from far behind to defeat Corcoran in the primary election by 3,881 votes. His next hurdle was Republican John Nance Garner, who nearly ousted Meeds in 1976. Garner spent extensively on his campaign against Swift, but Swift attacked Garner's heavy spending which turned Garner's monetary advantage into a liability. The outcome was a 51 percent victory for Swift.
Once elected to Congress it did not take Swift long to become active. He was a protegé of Senator Warren G. Magnuson, and it was through Magnuson's influence that Swift was appointed to the Energy and Commerce Committee in his freshman term. During his congressional career he also chaired the Energy and Commerce Subcommittee on Transportation and Hazardous Materials and the Elections Subcommittee. Membership on these key committees allowed Swift to play a major role in some of the most important issues that arose during his tenure, including broadcast deregulation, telecommunications, uniform polling results, the Northwest Power Bill, the Motor Voter Law, campaign finance reform, and the spotted owl controversy.
Swift was described by Alan Ehrenharlt of "Congressional Quarterly" in 1986's Politics in America as "patient, diligent, and disdainful of publicity, he is one of the most impressive legislators to arrive in Congress in recent years." This kind of sentiment and his reputation for being the legislative expert on broadcasting and telecommunication issues led to the naming of Swift as one of the twelve most underrated members of Congress in 1985.
Swift was first elected in 1978 and served 8 successive terms until 1994 when he chose not to run for reelection.
The Al Swift Congressional Papers comprise materials generated during Swift's 16 year career in the United States House of Representatives (1978-1994). The collection documents Swift's operations in both Washington D.C. and in his district offices in Everett and Bellingham.
The records consist of correspondence; photographs; speeches; awards; and press, committee, campaign and project files. The materials document important issues of the late 1970s through the mid-1990s, including environmental concerns such as clean air, nuclear waste, the spotted owl, and hydroelectric power; telecommunication and broadcasting issues; and campaign finance reform and uniform poll closing.
Casework files were destroyed by Representative Swift's staff due to privacy issues.
The Al Swift Congressional Papers are organized in accordance with the following series arrangement:
Series I: Pre-Congressional Career, 1971-1973
Series II: Office Files, 1979-1994
Series III: Press Secretary Files, 1978-2003
Series IV: Committee on Energy and Commerce, 1979-1980
Series V: House Administration Committee - Election Subcommittee, 1979-1994
Series VI: Committee on Energy and Commerce - Transportation and Hazardous Materials Subcommittee, 1987-1994
Series VII: District Office Records, 1971-1994
Series VIII: Campaign Records, 1976-1992
Series IX: Project Files, 1965-1995
The majority of the collection is open to the public - files in Boxes 326-327 are restricted until 2045.
The records were shipped directly to the Center for Pacific Northwest Studies from Swift's offices in Washington, D.C. upon the conclusion of his congressional career in 1998.
The Center for Pacific Northwest Studies houses a video recording and full-text transcript of an interview with Al Swift conducted by Midori Okazaki in 2003. There is also an untranscribed interview with Swift on cassette tape in the Western Washington University Centennial Oral History Project Collection.
This collection is indexed under the following headings in the online catalog. Researchers desiring materials about related topics, persons, or places should search the catalog using these headings.
Swift, Al, 1935- --Archives
Legislators--Washington (State); Election law--United States--History--Sources; Telecommunication--Law and legislation--United States--History--Sources; Radioactive waste disposal--Law and legislation--United States--History--Sources; Water-power--Washington (State)--History--Sources; Dams--Washington (State)--Elwha River--History--Sources; Environmental law--United States--History--Sources; Broadcasting--Law and legislation--United States--History--Sources
Records (Documents)
Washington (State); Artifacts; Moving Images; Photographs; Sound Recordings; Business, Industry, and Labor; Environmental Conditions; Fisheries and Wildlife; Government and Politics; International Relations; Military; Native Americans; Public Works; Public Utilities; Science
The following section contains a detailed listing of the materials in the collection.
- Pre-Congressional Career, 1971-1973; Series I
  - Bellingham City Charter Revision, 1971-1973
    - Agenda, Undated (Box-folder 1/1)
    - Minutes: Board of Freeholders, 1971-1972 (Box-folder 1/2)
    - Proposed City Charter: Drafts, 1971-1972 (Box-folder 1/3)
    - Reference Material, 1971-1972 (Box-folder 1/4)
    - State Law (Concerning City Charters), 1971 (Box-folder 1/5)
    - Misc. Suggestions and Information, 1971-1972 (Box-folder 1/6)
    - Executive Committee, 1971-1972 (Box-folder 1/7)
    - Public Relations, 1971-1972 (Box-folder 1/8)
    - Proposed City Charter, 1972 May 11 (Box-folder 1/9)
    - Charter of the City of Bellingham, 1973 (Box-folder 1/10)
- Office Files, 1979-1994; Series II
  - Policies and Procedures, 1979-1994; Subseries 1
    (Note: The 1979 Employment file was removed from the collection due to the personal information it contained.)
    - "Al's Doodles", Undated (Box-folder 2/1)
    - Awards and Certificates, Undated (Box-folder 2/2)
    - General, 1979-1980 (Box-folder 2/3)
    - General Office Structure, 1981-1982 (Box-folder 2/4)
    - Government Address List, 1979 (Box-folder 2/5)
    - Government Printing Office, 1979-1980 (Box-folder 2/6)
    - Legislative Priorities, 1979-1993 (Box-folder 2/7)
    - Mail Count Totals, 1979-1980 (Box-folder 2/8)
    - Mailing List: Federal Register, 1979-1980 (Box-folder 2/9)
    - Memoranda, 1979-1980 (Box-folder 2/10)
    - Memoranda, 1980 (Box-folder 2/11)
    - Memoranda, 1/81-3/81 (Box-folder 2/12)
    - Memoranda, 4/81-6/81 (Box-folder 2/13)
    - Memoranda, 7/81-9/81 (Box-folder 2/14)
    - Memoranda, 10/81-12/81 (Box-folder 2/15)
    - Memoranda, 1988 (Box-folder 2/16)
    - Office Floor Plan, Undated (Box-folder 2/17)
    - Project Lists, 1991-1994 (Box-folder 2/18)
  - Sponsored or CoSponsored Bills- U.S. Congress, 1979-1994; Subseries 2
    - "Zante File" 96th Congress 2nd Session, Undated (Box-folder 3/1)
    - H.R. 2821 Skagit River Basin Flood Control, 3/17/79 (Box-folder 3/2)
    - H.R. 3635 Terminal Illness Waiting Period, 4/10/79 (Box-folder 3/3)
    - H.R. 5439 Amend the Rail Service Assistance, 9/27/79 (Box-folder 3/4)
    - H.R. 6228 Broadcasting Station Licenses, 12/20/79 (Box-folder 3/5)
    - H.R. 6677 (Substitute for S. 885) Pacific Northwest Power Plan, 3/30/80 (Box-folder 3/6)
    - H.R. 6970 Boulder River Wilderness, 3/28/80 (Box-folder 3/7)
    - H.R. 7336 Helium Energy Act of 1980, 5/13/80 (Box-folder 3/8)
    - H.R. 7826 Home Purchase Incentive Act of 1980, 7/24/80 (Box-folder 3/9)
    - H.R. 8157 Pacific Northwest Power Bill, 9/18/80 (Box-folder 3/10)
    - H.R. 2477 Boulder River (Mt. Baker-Snoqualmie National Forest), 3/11/81 (Box-folder 3/11)
    - H.R. 3475 Crossownership Bill, 5/6/81 (Box-folder 3/12)
    - H.R. 3583 Regional Presidential Primaries, 5/13/81 (Box-folder 3/13)
    - H.R. 3877 Helium Energy Act of 1980, 6/10/81 (Box-folder 3/14)
    - H.R. 4726 Broadcasting Public Responsibility Act, 10/7/81 (Box-folder 3/15)
    - H.R. 5752 Renewal of Broadcasting Station Licenses, 3/8/82 (Box-folder 3/16)
    - H.R. 6256 Federal Election Commission Appropriations, 5/4/82 (Box-folder 3/17)
    - H.R. 6264 Mineral Leasing- Mt. Baker-Snoqualmie National Forest, 5/4/82 (Box-folder 3/18)
    - H.R. 7013 Used Motor Vehicle Sales Act of 1982, 8/17/82 (Box-folder 3/19)
    - H. Con. Res. 400 Vacancy on the Federal Reserve Board, 8/19/82 (Box-folder 3/20)
    - Legislative Profile- Al Swift, 1/3/83-11/9/84 (Box-folder 3/21)
    - H.J. Res. 113 Constitutional Amendment to Fix Compensation for Congress, 1/31/83 (Box-folder 3/22)
    - H.R. 2370 Broadcasting Public Responsibility and Deregulation Act of 1983, 3/24/83 (Box-folder 3/23)
    - H.R. 2615 Weatherization and Jobs, 4/19/83 (Box-folder 3/24)
    - H.R. 2621 FEC Authorization and Appropriation Report, 4/19/83 (Box-folder 3/25)
    - H. Res. 231 FCC Inquiry to Ascertain Impact on Telephone Rates, 6/14/83 (Box-folder 3/26)
    - H.R. 3376 Trust Lands for Makah Tribe, 6/21/83 (Box-folder 3/27)
    - H.R. 3440 Universal Telephone Service and Ratepayer Protection Act of 1983, 6/28/83 (Box-folder 3/28)
    - H.R. 3748 Amend U.S. Code to Include Customs in Retirement, 8/2/83 (Box-folder 3/29)
    - H.R. 4229 Cable Telecommunications Act of 1983, 10/26/83 (Box-folder 3/30)
    - H.R. 4324 FCC Personal Attack and Political Editorial Rules, 11/8/83 (Box-folder 3/31)
    - H.R. 4367 Voter Registration, 11/10/83 (Box-folder 3/32)
    - H.C. Res. 227 Early Projections- Impact of Media on Voting, 11/16/83 (Box-folder 3/33)
    - H.R. 4638 Boulder River/Mt. Baker-Snoqualmie, 1/24/84 (Box-folder 3/34)
    - H.R. 4807 Prohibit Elk Hunting in Olympic National Park, 2/8/84 (Box-folder 3/35)
    - H.R. 5246 Public Broadcasting Support Act of 1984, 3/27/84 (Box-folder 3/36)
    - H.R. 5606 FEC Authorization, 5/7/84 (Box-folder 3/37)
    - H.R. 6122 Broadcasting Public Responsibility and Deregulation Act of 1984, 8/9/84 (Box-folder 3/38)
    - Cosponsoring List of Legislation (Memo), 10/1/84 (Box-folder 3/39)
    - H.R. 1518 INS Retirement- Hazardous Occupations, 3/7/85 (Box-folder 3/40)
    - H.R. 1532 FEC Authorization, 3/19/85 (Box-folder 3/41)
    - H.R. 3525 Uniform Poll Closing Times, 10/8/85 (Box-folder 3/42)
    - H.R. 4393 Voting- Absentee and Overseas, 3/12/86 (Box-folder 3/43)
    - H.R. 4394 Federal Radioactive Waste Liability Act of 1986, 3/12/86 (Box-folder 3/44)
    - H.C. Res. 308 Rural Telephone Resolution, 4/6/86 (Box-folder 3/45)
    - H.R. 4704 Olympic National Park, 4/29/86 (Box-folder 3/46)
    - H.R. 4758 FEC Authorization, 5/7/86 (Box-folder 3/47)
    - H.R. 5068 FCC/Trafficking Prohibition, 6/19/86 (Box-folder 4/1)
    - H.R. 3086 Federal Aid to States for Voter Registration, 7/25/86 (Box-folder 4/2)
    - H.R. 5423 Nuclear Waste Policy Amendments of 1986, 8/13/86 (Box-folder 4/3)
    - Bills CoSponsored by Congressman Al Swift- 100th Congress, 1987-1988 (Box-folder 4/4)
    - H.R. 1 Water Quality Act, 1/6/87 (Box-folder 4/5)
    - H.R. 20 Federal Employees Political Activities Act of 1987, 1/6/87 (Box-folder 4/6)
    - H.R. 28 Expedited Funds Availability Act-, 1/6/87 (Box-folder 4/7)
    - H.R. 87 National Appliance Energy Conservation Act of 1987, 1/6/87 (Box-folder 4/8)
    - H.R. 280 Restrictions Relating to Drug Testing by Federal Agencies, 1/6/87 (Box-folder 4/9)
    - H.R. 313 Foreign Assistance Accountability Act, 1/6/87 (Box-folder 4/10)
    - H.R. 388 Continuation of 3-year Recovery Rule, 1/6/87 (Box-folder 4/11)
    - H.R. 435 Poll Closing Time, 1/6/87 (Box-folder 4/12)
    - H.R. 558 Urgent Relief of the Homeless Act, 1/8/87 (Box-folder 4/13)
    - H.R. 607 Surplus Cheese, 1/8/87 (Box-folder 4/14)
    - H.R. 782 Prohibit Access Charges, 1/27/87 (Box-folder 4/15)
    - H.R. 783 Dept. of Energy Environmental Compliance Act of 1987, 1/27/87 (Box-folder 4/16)
    - H.R. 910 Self-Sufficiency for the Poor Act of 1987, 2/2/87 (Box-folder 4/17)
    - H.R. 925 Family and Medical Leave Act of 1987, 2/3/87 (Box-folder 4/18)
    - H.R. 1090 Diversity in Media Ownership Act of 1987, 2/11/87 (Box-folder 4/19)
    - H.R. 1122 Economic Dislocation and Adjustment Assistance Act, 2/18/87 (Box-folder 4/20)
    - H.R. 1178 Anti-Greenmail Bill, 2/19/87 (Box-folder 4/21)
    - H.R. 1187 Broadcast Ownership Stability Act of 1987, 2/19/87 (Box-folder 4/22)
    - H.R. 1212 Employee Polygraph Protection Act, 2/24/87 (Box-folder 4/23)
    - H.R. 1272 Health Protection Act of 1987, 2/25/87 (Box-folder 4/24)
    - H.R. 1283 Repeal Nondeductability of Sales Tax, 2/26/87 (Box-folder 4/25)
    - H.R. 1325 Medicare Diabetic Foot Disease Prevention Act, 3/2/87 (Box-folder 4/26)
    - H.R. 1436 Limit Milk Protein Products Imported into the U.S., 3/5/87 (Box-folder 4/27)
    - H.R. 1634 Establish a Western Regional Export Licensing Office, 3/17/87 (Box-folder 4/28)
    - H.R. 1692 Employee Education Assistance Act of 1987, 3/18/87 (Box-folder 4/29)
    - H.R. 1711 Medicaid Community Spouse Protection Amendment of 1987, 3/18/87 (Box-folder 4/30)
    - H.R. 1727 Strategic Ocean and Coastal Resources Act of 1987, 3/19/87 (Box-folder 4/31)
    - H.R. 1859 FCC Appropriations, 3/30/87 (Box-folder 4/32)
    - H.R. 1885 Satellite Television Fair Marketing Act, 3/31/87 (Box-folder 4/33)
    - H.R. 1950 Require that Telephone Monitoring be Accompanied by Warning Tone, 4/6/87 (Box-folder 4/34)
    - H. Res. 145 Support of Congress for the W.H.D. in its Effort to Combat AIDS, 4/9/87 (Box-folder 4/35)
    - H.R. 2030 Telecommunications Equipment and Info. Services Act, 4/9/87 (Box-folder 4/36)
    - H.R. 2082 Federal Radioactive Waste Liability Act, 4/9/87 (Box-folder 4/37)
    - H.R. Kenneth G. Ward Border Station (Lynden, WA), 4/21/87 (Box-folder 4/38)
    - H.R. 2141 Price Anderson Amendments Act of 1987, 4/23/87 (Box-folder 4/39)
    - H.R. 2183 Rural Letter Carriers Tax Simplification Act, 4/28/87 (Box-folder 4/40)
    - H.R. 2189 Nuclear Waste Policy Amendments of 1987, 4/28/87 (Box-folder 4/41)
    - H.R. 2213 Hearing Aid Compatibility Act, 4/29/87 (Box-folder 4/42)
    - H.R. 2260 POW and MIA Material Made Public, 4/30/87 (Box-folder 4/43)
    - H.R. 2464 Campaign Cost Reduction And Reform Act of 1987, 5/19/87 (Box-folder 4/44)
    - H.J. Res. 291 Honorary Status of Librarian of Congress, 5/21/87 (Box-folder 4/45)
    - H.R. 2512 Tariff on Loganberries and Raspberries, 5/27/87 (Box-folder 4/46)
    - H.R. 2532 Early Retirement for Customs, Immigration, and IRS Revenue Officers, 5/28/87 (Box-folder 4/47)
    - H.R. 2640 Extend for Four Years the Period During Which Qualified Mortgage Bonds May Be Issued, 6/10/87 (Box-folder 4/48)
    - H.R. 2771 Moratorium on Pre-Payments Under Sec. 515 of the Housing Act of 1949, 6/24/87 (Box-folder 4/49)
    - H.R. 2800 Hazardous Waste Reduction Act, 6/25/87 (Box-folder 4/50)
    - H.R. 2828 Telecommunications Employees' Protection Act, 6/29/87 (Box-folder 4/51)
    - H.R. 2888 Nuclear Waste Policy Commission Act, 7/1/87 (Box-folder 4/52)
    - H.J. Res. 122 "Snow White Week", 7/13/87 (Box-folder 4/53)
    - H.R. 3232 Label Pizza Products Containing Imitation Cheese and Meat, 8/7/87 (Box-folder 4/54)
    - H.R. Children's TV Ad Practices Act, 9/16/87 (Box-folder 4/55)
    - H.R. 3300 Hazardous Waste Management and Reduction Act, 9/17/87 (Box-folder 4/56)
    - H.R. 3321 Cable Channel Shifting Act, 9/22/87 (Box-folder 4/57)
    - H.R. 3344 Effect Any Reduction for Milk Price Support Activities, 9/25/87 (Box-folder 4/58)
    - H.R. 3423 Bowerman Basin (Est. Grays Harbor National Wildlife Refuge), 10/6/87 (Box-folder 4/59)
    - H.R. 3445 Natural Gas Consumers Protection Act, 10/7/87 (Box-folder 4/60)
    - H.R. 3470 Omnibus Taxpayers' Bill of Rights, 10/13/87 (Box-folder 4/61)
    - H.R. 3493 Broadcast License Reform Act, 10/15/87 (Box-folder 4/62)
    - H.R. 3643 Insurance Data Collection Act, 11/16/87 (Box-folder 4/63)
    - H.R. 3660 Act for Better Childcare Services, 11/19/87 (Box-folder 4/64)
    - H.R. 3781 DOE Waste Cleanup Act, 12/17/87 (Box-folder 4/65)
    - H.R. Amend. Solid Waste to Improve Compliance by Fed. Facilities with Requirement of Subtitle C, 12/17/87 (Box-folder 4/66)
    - H.R. Amend. Solid Waste Disposal Act to Improve Compliance with Hazardous Waste Laws at Federal Facilities, 12/17/87 (Box-folder 4/67)
    - H.R. 3784 Amend Solid Waste Disposal Act to Clarify Reg. of Certain DOE Waste Under Subtitle C, 12/17/87 (Box-folder 4/68)
    - H.R. 3785 Amend Solid Waste Disposal Act to Clarify Provisions Concerning the Application of Certain Requirements and Sanctions to Federal Facilities, Undated (Box-folder 4/69)
    - H.R. 3979 Reimburse Clallam Co. Historical Society, 2/18/88 (Box-folder 5/1)
    - H.R. 4049 Women in Development Act, 3/1/88 (Box-folder 5/2)
    - H.R. 4060 Emergency Hunger Relief Act of 1988, 3/2/88 (Box-folder 5/3)
    - H.R. 4127 American Heritage Trust Act of 1988, 3/9/88 (Box-folder 5/4)
    - H.R. 4146 Washington Park and Wilderness Bill of 1988, 3/15/88 (Box-folder 5/5)
    - H.R. 4221 Section 457 Clarification Act of 1988, 3/22/88 (Box-folder 5/6)
    - H.R. 4224 Feasibility of Burning Weapons Grade Nuclear Material, 3/22/88 (Box-folder 5/7)
    - H.R. 4280 Amend Internal Revenue Code of 1986, 3/29/88 (Box-folder 5/8)
    - H.R. 4436 Authorize Appropriations for the Federal Election Commission, 4/20/88 (Box-folder 5/9)
    - H.R. 4695 Forest Wildfire Emergency Pay Equity Act of 1988, 5/26/88 (Box-folder 5/10)
    - H.R. 4832 San Juan Property Titles, 6/15/88 (Box-folder 5/11)
    - H.R. 4950 Establish Dept. of Defense Acquisition Agency, 6/29/88 (Box-folder 5/12)
    - H.R. 5019 Regulation of Interstate Telephone Service Rates, 7/12/88 (Box-folder 5/13)
    - H.R. 5051 Approval of Accreditation Systems for Laboratories Testing Fasteners, 7/14/88 (Box-folder 5/14)
    - H.R. 5126 Grants for the Implementation of the Puget Sound Water Quality Management Plan, 8/2/88 (Box-folder 5/15)
    - H.R. 5203 Land Trust for the Quinault Indian Nation, 8/11/88 (Box-folder 5/16)
    - H. Res. 532 Express Outrage Toward Iraq for its Use of Poison Gas Against the Kurds, 9/9/88 (Box-folder 5/17)
    - H. Con. Res. 376 Support for the Cabotage Laws Protecting the Coastwide Trade, 9/27/88 (Box-folder 5/18)
    - H.R. 5409 Alcoholic Beverage Labeling Act of 1988, 9/28/88 (Box-folder 5/19)
    - H.R. 1 Amend Civil Rights Act of 1964, 1/91 (Box-folder 5/20)
    - H.R. 427 Disclaim any Interests of the U.S. in Certain Lands on San Juan, WA, 1/3/91 (Box-folder 5/21)
    - H.R. 793 Extend Civil Service Retirement Provisions to INS Officers, 2/4/91 (Box-folder 5/22)
    - H.R. 1007 Amend Internal Revenue Code of 1986, 2/20/91 (Box-folder 5/23)
    - H.R. 1087 High Speed Rail Transportation Policy and Development Act, 2/21/91 (Box-folder 5/24)
    - H.R. 1110 Provide for U.S. Contribution to the U.N. Population Fund, 2/26/91 (Box-folder 5/25)
    - H.R. 1179 Prohibit Denial of International Population Assistance Funds, 2/28/91 (Box-folder 5/26)
    - H.R. 1346 Peace, Democracy, and Development in El Salvador Act of 1991, 3/7/91 (Box-folder 5/27)
    - H.R. 1362 Appropriations for the Federal Election Commission, 3/7/91 (Box-folder 5/28)
    - H.R. 1363 Amend the Internal Revenue Code of 1986, 3/7/91 (Box-folder 5/29)
    - H.R. 1437 Construction of Dept. of Agriculture Building in Washington State, 3/13/91 (Box-folder 5/30)
    - H.R. 1438 Loans for Greenhouses/Nurseries in Case of Disaster, 3/13/91 (Box-folder 5/31)
    - H.R. 1531 Pension Tax Equity Act of 1991, 3/20/91 (Box-folder 5/32)
    - H. Con. Res. 113 Seek an International Moratorium on the Use of Large Scale Driftnets, 4/9/91 (Box-folder 5/33)
    - H.R. 1771 Amend the Internal Revenue Code of 1986, 4/15/91 (Box-folder 5/34)
    - H. Res. 161 Unfair Practices in International Trade, 5/23/91 (Box-folder 5/35)
    - H.R. 2533 Presidential Election Campaign Fund Protection Act, 6/4/91 (Box-folder 5/36)
    - H.R. 2607 Rail Safety Enforcement and Review Act, 6/11/91 (Box-folder 5/37)
    - H.R. 2799 High Quality Forestry, 6/26/91 (Box-folder 5/38)
    - H.R. 2806 Earthquake Hazard Reduction Amendments Act, 6/27/91 (Box-folder 5/39)
    - H.R. 2829 Telephone Disclosure and Dispute Resolution Act, 7/9/91 (Box-folder 5/40)
    - H.R. 3203 Consumer Protection Telemarketing Act, 8/2/91 (Box-folder 5/41)
    - Cosponsor List, 8/29/91 (Box-folder 5/42)
    - H.R. Major League Baseball Equity Act, 9/19/91 (Box-folder 5/43)
    - H.R. 3477 Combined Sewer Overflow Control Act, 10/2/91 (Box-folder 5/44)
    - H.R. 3490 Telephone Disclosure and Dispute Resolution Act, 10/3/91 (Box-folder 5/45)
    - H.R. 3554 Lead Exposure Reduction Act of 1991, 10/11/91 (Box-folder 5/46)
    - H.R. 3636 Nuclear Testing Moratorium Act, 10/24/91 (Box-folder 5/47)
    - H.R. 3644 Presidential Election Campaign Fund, 10/28/91 (Box-folder 5/48)
    - H.R. 3645 Tourism Policy and Export Promotion Act, 10/29/91 (Box-folder 5/49)
    - H.R. 3750 House of Representatives Campaign Spending Limit and Election Reform Act, 11/12/91 (Box-folder 5/50)
    - H.R. 3809 Toy Injury Reduction Act, 11/19/91 (Box-folder 5/51)
    - H.R. 3841 Reforestation Tax Act of 1991, 11/21/91 (Box-folder 5/52)
    - H.R. 3865 National Waste Reduction, Recycling, and Management Act, 11/22/91 (Box-folder 5/53)
    - H.R. 3907 Universal Health Insurance Act of 1991, 11/25/91 (Box-folder 5/54)
    - H.R. 3931 Timber Resource Employment Enhancement Act, Undated (Box-folder 5/55)
    - H.R. 4116 Appropriations for the Federal Elections Commission, 1/24/92 (Box-folder 5/56)
    - H.R. 4250 Amtrak Capital Acquisition and Technology Development Act, 2/19/92 (Box-folder 5/57)
    - H.R. 4331 Forest Resources Amendments Act, 2/27/92 (Box-folder 5/58)
    - H.R. 4414 Establish an Intercity Rail Passenger Capital Improvement Trust Fund, 3/10/92 (Box-folder 5/59)